W是谁?
"W" who?
W.U.R.G 94.9，紧急召集，
WURG 94.9, the Urge,
哈顿菲尔德摇滚者之家
Haddonfield's home for rock.
我是威利小子，
I'm Willie the Kid,
而你，你拿我毫...毫无办法
and there's n-n-nothing you can do about it.
科里，你真是个救星
Corey, you're a lifesaver.
嗨
Hi.
最近好吗?进来吧
How've you been? Come on in.
罗杰 科里来了
Roger  Corey's here
抱歉这么晚了，安德里亚胃痛
Sorry this is last-minute, but Andrea got a stomach bug
-真的给我打电话了 -哦,没关系
-and literally just called me. -Oh, it's okay.
这是罗杰公司举办的万圣节派对
It's Roger's company Halloween party,
我倒是无所谓，但是… 罗杰
and I could care less, but... Roger
希望他照顾孩子能比整理院子更在行
Hope he's better at childcare than he is at yard work.
你知道，明年春天，
You know, next spring,
你应该考虑一些常绿植物
you should consider some perennials.
推荐绣球
Hydrangeas could really
-还是山茱萸把 省点钱给学费?
-balance out that dogwood. -Saving for college?
-你说你要去哪里?-哦,我申请了
-Where did you say you're going? -Oh, I'm applying
几个不同的工程类课程
to a few different engineering programs.
我今年在攒钱，明年秋季班就能去了
Just saving money this year so I can go next fall.
杰瑞米，照看你的人来了
Jeremy, the sitter's here
杰里米
Jeremy
-啊 你 我会抓住你的
-Ah  You  I'm gonna get you
我会抓到你的
I'm gonna get you.
迫降 爆炸
Crash landing  Kaboom
你能教我怎么做雷霆轰炸机吗?
Can you show me how to make a Thunder Bomber?
永远排名第一的那种
Number one of all time.
-我爸爸做那最棒 -没问题
-My dad can do the best. -No pressure.
好啊，我们试试的，小家伙
Yeah, I'll sure give it a shot, little dude.
你对科里先生好一些可以吗?
You gonna be good for Mr. Corey?
科里我能跟你说句话吗? -好的
-Corey. Could I talk to you for a sec? -Yeah.
雷声轰炸机来了
Here comes the Thunder Bomber
我要把糖果放在门廊上
I'm gonna put the candy on the porch.
万圣节“不给糖就捣蛋”孩子们可以自己动手去拿
Trick-or-treat kids can help themselves.
你想吃什么冰箱里可以随便拿什么
Help yourself to anything in the fridge.
我太太做的南瓜面包超赞的
She made zucchini bread. It's actually good.
-你有我手机号码
-You have my number.
-嗯 -如果有什么紧急情况
-Okay. -If there's an emergency,
但我们就在街尾
but we'll just be right down the street.
-坏啦
- Crash
有还件事我要告诉你
And there is one thing I need to tell you.
去年万圣节，发生了那么多
Since last Halloween-- all the events and,
关于迈克尔·迈尔斯的头条
you know, the headlines of Michael Myers--
杰里米就一直怕黑
Jeremy's been afraid of the dark.
他晚上会尿床
He's been wetting the bed at night.
而且，睡眠困难
And, um, bedtime has been difficult.
我能听见你在说我
I can hear you
我可以给他读个故事什么的
Uh, I can read him a story or something.
他有最喜欢的书吗?-他睡觉了以后
-Does he have a favorite book? -Then once he goes to bed,
会说梦话
he talks in his sleep.
他说他能听到某种声音
Says he hears voices.
他对那些可以引起做噩梦的事情
He's just really sensitive to things
特别敏感 -你说的听起来
-that give him bad dreams. -Right. All that just sounds
像绝大多数孩子想象出来的东西一样，对吧?
like normal kid imagination stuff, right?
不要看电视，不要给他吃糖
-No TV and no more candy.
你们可以玩到八点半或八点三刻
You guys can play till 8:30, 8:45.
然后就让他睡觉了
Then he should go to bed.
这钱好赚 -是的
-Easy money. -Yes.
你要不要跟我一起玩?
Gonna come play with me or what?
- 听着像吓我一样
-That sounds like a threat.
今天是万圣节
It's Halloween.
今晚我们会玩得很开心的
We're gonna have a good time tonight.
听着，小伙 -如果你害怕看怪物电影，
-Look, man, we can
我们可以把电视机关掉
shut it off if you're scared of monster movies.
不，不，你才害怕
No. No. You're scared.
我都21岁了 我才不会害怕
I'm 21 years old. I don't get scared.
你害怕是因为你知道迈克尔·迈尔斯
You're scared because you know Michael Myers is...
还活着
still out there.
他会抓到你的
Boogeyman's gonna get you.
他才不会
He's not gonna get me.
迈克尔·迈尔斯喜欢杀的是保姆，而不是孩子
Michael Myers kills babysitters, not kids.
好吧，这画面真的很恶心
Okay, that's actually pretty disgusting
不适合孩子
and probably not appropriate for kids.
为什么我们不关掉它，然后…
Why don't we shut this off, and...
我们可以在睡觉前玩捉迷藏
we can play hide-and-seek before bed.
你父母马上就回来了…
Your parents are gonna be home soon and...
我不想玩捉迷藏
I don't want to play no hide-and-seek.
捉迷藏好蠢的 我想看这部电影
It's stupid. I want to watch this movie.
我也不想假装和一个男保姆
And I don't really feel like pretending to be best friends
做好朋友
with an ugly-ass boy babysitter.
好吧，五分钟，然后你就去睡觉
Okay, five minutes, and then you're going to bed.
你还真不擅长照看孩子
You suck at babysitting.
我不是保姆
I'm not a babysitter.
杰里米
Jeremy
把那部电影关掉
Turn that movie off
杰里米?
Jeremy?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
杰里米?
Jeremy?
杰里米
Jeremy
杰里米?
Jeremy?
出来吧，出来吧，不管你在哪里
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
这不好笑，杰里米
This isn't funny, Jeremy.
杰里米
Jeremy
杰里米?
Jeremy?
救命 科里,救命
Help  Corey, help
杰里米?
Jeremy?
他会抓到你的
He's gonna get you
他会在你最意想不到的时候抓住你
He's gonna get you when you least expect it.
-是你睡觉的时候了，科里? -好吧,杰里米……
- Is it your bedtime, Corey? -Okay, Jeremy...
“出来，出来，不管你在哪里”
"Come out, come out, wherever you are."
被你抓到了，伙计，好吧，放我出去
You got me, buddy. Okay, let me out.
-你害怕吗? -好吗?
- Are you scared? -Okay?
“我21岁我不害怕”
"I'm 21. I'm not scared."
杰里米，放我出去 让我出去
Jeremy, let me out. Let me out
你这个小混蛋 放我出去
You little shit  Let me out of here
迈克尔·迈尔斯
Michael Myers.
-杰里米，这不好笑，好吗?-
-Jeremy, it's not funny, okay? -
你会让我们都有麻烦的
Hey, you're gonna get us both in trouble.
让我出去 让我出去
Let me out Let me out Let me out
你这个小混蛋
You little shit
我要杀了你，杰里米
-I'm gonna kill you, Jeremy
-那是什么?
-What was that?
杰里米
Jeremy
-哦,不 哦,老天,不 杰里米
-Oh, no  Oh, God, no  Please  -Jeremy
-哦,不 -哦,老天 -杰里米
-Oh, no. Oh, God.  Jeremy
哦,我的老天 杰里米
Oh, my God  Jeremy
-杰里米-杰里米
- Jeremy. - Jeremy
老天,求求你,不
God, please, no
你做了什么?
What have you done?
哈顿菲尔德是一个宁静的小镇
Haddonfield was a peaceful town.
很多年前的一个万圣节之夜，
And then one Halloween night many years ago,
这一切都改变了
all of that was lost.
迈克尔·迈尔斯是个十足的恶魔
Michael Myers was pure evil.
他夺走了我们的梦想
He took our dreams
把它们变成了噩梦
and turned them into nightmares.
当他被关在监狱里的时候…
As he was locked away in his prison...
...我也消失在我的世界里
...I disappeared into mine.
然后，如我所料，
And then, as I predicted,
40年后，他逃了出来
40 years later, he escaped,
哈顿菲尔德再次被迫面对
and Haddonfield was once again forced to confront
这个戴面具的人
this man in a mask.
他毫无理性的暴行蹂躏了我们的社区
His senseless brutality ravaged my community...
...还杀了我女儿
...and killed my daughter.
然后他就消失了
And then he vanished.
不可能吗?
Impossible?
也许吧
Perhaps.
真相会演变成传说
Truth would evolve into legend
当人们寻找动机和意义的时候
as people searched for motive and meaning,
在暗处寻找这个恶魔
looking in the shadows for their boogeyman.
这是个意外
It was an accident.
在接下来的几年里，
In the years that followed,
哈顿菲尔德的人们陷入了瘟疫
the people of Haddonfield descended into a plague
悲伤，责备，偏执
of grief, of blame, of paranoia.
你认为他回来了吗?
Do you think he's come back?
迈克尔不用枪
Michael doesn't use guns.
迈克尔造成的痛苦
The suffering Michael caused
变成了传染给人类的传染病
became an infection passing on to people
从没见过他的人
who never even crossed his path.
当整个小镇都在自我封闭的时候，
And as the town turned in on itself,
我发誓不再让恐惧支配我的生活
I made a promise not to let fear rule my life anymore.
我买了一套房子
I bought a home.
一个充满爱和信任的地方
A place to live with love and trust.
没有陷阱
Not a trap.
不是藏身之处
Not a place to hide.
自从我最后一次见到那恶魔
It has been four years
已经过去四年了
since I last saw my monster.
所以我在此想以一个幸存者的视角分享我的故事
So here I am, a survivor attempting to share my story
并找到治愈
and find healing.
迈克尔·迈尔斯是恶魔的化身
Michael Myers was the personification of evil.
这是他们的
It's theirs.
他们的结婚戒指
It's their wedding rings.
这取决于我们每个人
It's up to each of us
不管我们锁不锁门
whether or not we lock the door
找到我们的决心…
and find our resolve...
...或者让他进来
...or let him inside.
让它进来
Let it inside.
让邪恶…
Let evil...
进来
inside.
阿廖沙 讨厌
Allyson  Darn it
-亲爱的，我很抱歉 -怎么回事?
-Honey, I'm so sorry  -What is it?
哦,
Oh, fuck
嗯，我的派，我把派放进烤箱
Um, it's my pie. I put a pie in the oven.
哦，妈蛋
Oh, shit
哦，我一定是忘记设置计时器了
Oh, I must have forgotten to set the timer.
该死的
Damn it
真讨厌 不，不，哦，不
Darn it  No, no, no, no, Oh, no.
我可以从店里买一个派
I can get a pie from the store.
不 我想给你烤个南瓜派
No  I wanted to bake you a pumpkin pie.
这是万圣节的传统
It's a Halloween tradition.
-你……-我得走了
-Are you... -I got to go.
-我上班要迟到了 -好的
-I'm late for work.  Okay.
你准备好参加派对的服装了吗?
But do you have your costume for the party?
我说了，我不想一个人去
I told you, I don't want to go alone.
所以我不去了
So I'm not going.
哦
Oh.
WURG 94.9
WURG 94.9.
给你鼓励 和威利小子一起
Giving you the Urge, with Willie the Kid.
哈顿菲尔德是摇滚者之家
Haddonfield's home for rock.
还有四天就是万圣节了
It is four days until Halloween.
-你能相信吗?
-Can you believe it?
是时候锁好你的门，拿起你的刀开始战斗了
It's time to lock your doors, grab your knife for the fight.
你准备好了吗? 你准备好和
You ready? You ready in case
恶魔出来玩了么?
the Boogeyman decides to come out and play?
我知道我准备好了
I know I am.
但我们还是来谈谈迈克尔·迈尔斯吧
But let's talk about that Michael Myers for a minute.
怎么会有一个人被枪击，被捅了之后
How does one man get shot at, stabbed up
从街上摔下来，然后又爬起来
and then he fall down the street and get back up
把哈顿菲尔德的人都吓尿了
to scare the piss out of everybody in Haddonfield?
我来告诉你是什么，因为它不是人
Let me tell you how-- 'cause this isn't a man.
不仅仅是人 他是野兽
This is more than a man. This is a beast.
一头不会流血的野兽...
One that doesn't bleed...
我确认更改订单
I'm pretty sure that was in the change order.
等一下，香侬
Hold-hold on a second, Shannon.
嘿，科里，你迟到了
Hey, Corey, you're late
你又迟到了
You're late again
已经四年了
It's been four years.
你们在哪里?
Where y'all at?
也许是在为这个大日子训练?
Training for the big day, perhaps?
进入状态了吗?
Getting yourself in the spirit?
这个恶魔一直在冬眠，
This Boogeyman been sitting in hibernation,
但相信我，他会回来的
but trust me, y'all, he'll be back.
我是威利小子，我要来真的
I'm Willie the Kid, and I'll be creeping it real
94.9 WUR…
on 94.9 WUR...
科里，你有空吗?
Corey, you got a second?
觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
不错
Yeah.
把它注册一下
Get it registered.
做新钣金
Get some new plates.
-我用不上了，送你 -真的吗?
-I got no use for it no more. -Are you serious?
有个好的引擎的推动下，你应该能
With a good engine pushing you, finally make it
准时上班了吧，你明白我的意思吗?
to work on time, you know what I mean?
还能开么?
Does it work?
当然可以，就是有点旧了
Yeah, it works, just kind of shitty.
嘿，罗纳德
Hey, uh, Ronald?
谢谢
Thanks.
不用谢，孩子
No problem, kid.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
你是我认识的最漂亮的女孩
For being the prettiest girl I know.
真好,道格
That's nice, Doug.
所以你才让边停车吗?
Is that why you pulled me over?
不 我让你靠边停车 是因为我想你
No. I pulled you over 'cause I miss you.
你想我么?
You miss me?
只是开玩笑
Just kidding.
让你靠边停车，因为看起来
Pulled you over 'cause it looks like
你的引擎消音器坏了
your muffler's about to fall off.
最好在你遇到更大麻烦前
Better get that fixed before you have a bigger
把它修好
-problem on your hands.
你到底买不买?
You gonna buy something or what?
我本来可以开车来的
I could've drove here.
冷静，我可是代驾司机
Chill. I'm the designated driver.
-我知道怎么开车-请不要弄坏我的车
-I know how to drive. -Don't mess up my car, please.
-我不会弄坏你的车-对吗?
-I'm not gonna mess up your car. -All right?
-别搞砸了 别激动
-Don't mess it up. -Chill.
他的爸爸是……-我拿到驾照了
-His dad is... -I got my license.
这不是拉仇恨来的吧
It's no hating on. Come on.
比利 身份证呢? -计划是什么?
Billy. I.D.? - So what's the plan?
-给我你的身份证 -身份证?
-Give me the I.D. -I.D.?
-是的-上周被没收了
-Yeah. -It got confiscated last week.
我告诉过你-她有钱
-I told you. -She's got the money.
-你没带身份证? -等一下 你什么?
-You don't have your I.D.? -Wait. You what?
等等 -等一下 -嘿,你 我失去了它
-Wait. Hold on. Hey, yo  -I lost it.
等一下 新朋友
Wait.  New friend.
什么，喝牛奶啊
What, drinking a little milk.
-是的 -是的-我也喜欢牛奶
-Yeah. Yeah. -I like milk, too.
-听着，事情是这样的，伙计
-Look, here's the deal, man.
我们高三学生
We're seniors, okay?
我们一整年都在为今晚的比赛
We've been practicing for our show the whole year, you know.
而准备演出练习
Loading up for, uh, tonight's game and--
我们是行军乐队的一员
Well, we're in the fucking marching band.
我们希望一个很酷的新朋友
We were just hoping you could be a cool new friend, you know.
能给我们买几个六瓶装的啤酒
Just buy us a couple of six-packs.
只限于我和我的团队，可以么？伙计
Just-just for me and my crew. Come on, man.
哦,不
Uh, no.
不行?
No?
不，不行,谢谢? -什么?
No-no, thank you? What?
-不行,我不能-哦,等
-No, I can't. - Oh, wait.
-我知道你是谁 -还有你做的那些见不得人的事
-I know who you are. -You did something messy.
-真不敢相信他们把你放走了 -他是谁?
- I can't believe they let you off. -Well, who is he?
-哦,是的-想起来了
-Oh, yeah. -Yeah.
你就是那个变态保姆
You're that psycho babysitter.
他杀了那个孩子，是吗?
He killed that kid, didn't he?
是的 -杀了个孩子，娘炮
-Yep. -Killed a kid and too pussy
-给我们买点啤酒？ 伙计们，你们知道吗？
-to buy us some fucking beer?  Guys, you know what?
让我们忘了这事吧
Let's just fucking forget about it.
我们去看比赛吧，好吗?
Let's just go to the game, okay?
-你只是个小角色 -看看他
-You're just a little pedo. -Look at him.
-告诉他，特里 -你是什么东西
-Let him know, Terry. -That what you are?
一个微不足道的变态
A little fucking pedo creep?
-是 -到他面前去，特里
-That's right. -Get in his face, Terry.
你他妈算哪门子照顾孩子?
What kind of fucked-up kid are you?
-对 -对 -你下一个受害者是谁?
-That's right. -Right. -So where's your next victim?
-啊 什么?
-Whoa  -What the fuck?
你在开玩笑吗，伙计?
Are you kidding me, man?
-哦,妈蛋
- Oh, shit.
-看看你 什么鬼，特里?
-Look at you.  What the fuck, Terry?
到处都是牛奶
Got fucking milk everywhere.
-卧槽-看看你做了什么
Holy shit. -Look what you did.
嘿 混蛋
Hey  Assholes
住嘴
Knock it off
-我们什么都没做-我们只是谈谈，小姐
-We're not doing anything. -We're just talking, miss.
我们就是弄脏了这里 女士
-We're messing around. -Ma'am.
嘿,家伙
Hey, guys.
你能看看这个吗?
Would you look at this?
我是说，一个疯子遇上了畸形人
I mean, a psycho meets a freak show.
-哇 -不敢相信
-Wow. -Can't believe it.
你们真是天作之合
This is a match made in heaven.
-嘿,来吧 -看着我 -大大泡泡糖
-Hey, come on. Look at me. -Ta-ta for now.
我们走吧,你们
Let's go, y'all.
迈克尔·迈尔斯
Michael Myers.
你是疯子还是怪胎?
Are you the psycho or the freak show?
嘿，星期六你想去看学校的演出吗? ?
Hey, , do you want to go to the school play on Saturday?
是的,当然,特里-有趣
Yeah, sure, Terry. -Have fun.
所以，是你自己来，还是我来?
So, do you want to do it, or you want me to?
看一下
Look at it.
你在开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding?
你穿起来很好看
It looks great on you.
我知道，但我不会去的
I'm sure it does, but I'm not going.
你穿上整套衣服，你会喜欢的
Once you put the whole outfit on, you'll love it.
要我说穿得不性感就不算过万圣节了
I say if it's not sexy, it's not Halloween.
好吧 看来有人已经进了状态了
Well, someone's getting into the spirit of things.
这位先生出了点意外，需要看一下
This gentleman had an accident and needs a little fix-up.
你有严重的炎症
You have significant inflammation.
我要麻醉一下这里
Um, I'm gonna be nice and numb it here
我的助手会把它清理好，
so my assistant can clean it up really well,
然后我再回来缝合伤口
and then I will get back and close it with a suture.
你会觉得有点刺痛
You're gonna feel a little bit of a pinch here.
她很可爱,是吗?
Cute, isn't she?
我不是,噢
I don't-- Ow
老天 -对不起 -对不起
-Jesus Christ  - Sorry. Sorry.
我很抱歉 我很抱歉-艾莉森，你在干什么?
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -Allyson, what are you doing?
这是我的错 对不起 阿廖沙
It's my fault. Sorry. -Allyson
-不-对不起,对不起
-No. - Sorry, sorry.
不 不,我的错 这是我的错
No. No, my fault. It was my fault.
我很抱歉 -哦,天啊-真是一团糟
-I-I'm so sorry. Oh, geez. - What a mess.
把它清理干净，拿个该死的消毒包
Just clean it up and get a goddamn sterile kit.
给他打一针破伤风针
And give him a tetanus shot.
我马上就回来
I'll be back.
不该让那家伙那样跟你说话
You shouldn't let that guy talk to you like that.
这会让你难过的，即使你不这么认为
It's gonna make you sad, even if you don't think it does.
我处理过更糟糕的
I've dealt with much worse.
但是谢谢你
But thank you.
总之，我一直在处理这种事
Anyway, I've just been dealing with it.
我本该得到升职的
Well, I'm supposed to get this promotion.
-但不管怎样，这只是…-值得吗?
-But either way, it's just... -Is it worth it?
做什么了?
What'd you do?
-嗯……-你的手
-Uh... -To your hand?
我在工作，然后出了点小意外
Uh, I was at work, and then I had a little accident.
-所以 你的工作也很糟糕嗯?
-So your job sucks, too. -Hmm?
你在哪里工作?你做什么的?
Where do you work? What do you do?
修理店 -不要移动
Oh, a mechanic shop. -Don't move.
-不想被感染
-Don't want to get infected.
我的车一直响个不停
So my car's been rattling.
活泼的吗?-是的
-Rattling? -Yeah.
只是你的排气系统夹松了
Uh, it's just your exhaust system clamp's come loose.
这很容易解决大概需要五分钟
It's an easy fix. It takes like five minutes.
超级cinchy
Super cinchy.
你只需要一个升降机和两个螺丝
You just need a lift and two screws.
“Cinchy”?
"Cinchy"?
你不用现在就去修
You don't have to fix it right now.
是的，我没带我的东西，但是…
Yeah, I don't have my stuff, but...
我明天在商店
I am at the shop tomorrow.
那时我可以修好它
I can fix it then.
为什么自行车不能自己站起来?
Why can't the bicycle stand on its own?
不,不它可以
No, no. It can.
它有一个支架
It's got a kickstand.
因为它太累了
'Cause it was too tired.
是的
Yeah.
其实我要把自行车扔了，
Oh, I'm actually getting rid of the bike,
所以如果你想要，就给你
so if you want it, you can have it.
我有一辆摩托车
I got a motorcycle.
-哦,一辆摩托车吗?-是的
-Oh, a motorcycle? -Yeah.
教我骑?
Teach me to ride it?
是的
Yeah.
你背上有屎
You have shit on your back.
我将得到它
I'll get it.
我们应该找个时间出去做点什么
We should go out sometime and do something.
-我吗?-和我们两个一起
-With me? -With both of us.
我是说，我们两个都得去
I mean, we'd both have to be there.
否则，这不是一个很好的时间
Otherwise, it wouldn't be a very good time.
是啊，你不会想这么做的
Yeah, you don't want to do that.
我晚饭要迟到了
Uh, I'm gonna be late for dinner.
但是，我很感谢你的帮助
But, uh, I appreciate the hand.
感觉已经好多了
It feels better already.
所以你是故意的
So you did that on purpose.
什么?
What?
他受伤了,
He was injured,
他需要治疗，而马西斯医生
he needed medical attention, and Dr. Mathis
是城里最好的-你相信她吗?
-is the best in town. -Do you believe her?
-她说的话一个字也不要信-
-Do not believe a word she says. -
-你知道，她是个战略家-在,好,好
-You know, she's a strategist. -Fine, fine, fine.
她只是想扮演丘比特
She's just trying to play Cupid.
我觉得他很可爱似乎不错
Thought he was cute. Seemed nice.
你会给他打电话吗
Are you gonna call him
邀请他参加她的派对
and invite him to her party,
还是你要一个人去?
or you gonna just go alone?
现在选一张牌毫米
Now pick a card. Mm
哦,不我拿到死亡牌了
Oh, no. I got the death card.
-不，塔罗牌还不错-毫米毫米
-No, that's not bad in tarot. - Mm-mm.
不，那只是意味着一个重要阶段结束了
No, that just means a major phase is ending
新的一段就要开始了
and a new one is about to begin.
所以，这几乎是在棺材上钉了一颗钉子
So, that pretty much puts a nail in the coffin
和你约会的那个警官
with that police officer you were dating.
啊,道格
-Ugh, Doug.
你得找个能放手的人
You know, you need to find someone that can let go.
这让你想扯掉你的衬衫
That makes you want to rip off your shirt
露出你那该死的奶子，说，
and show grief your fucking tits and say,
“你知道吗?我们走吧”
"You know what? Let's go."
这是美味的
This is delicious.
科里它感染了吗?
Corey. Is it infected?
你的手感染了吗?医生怎么说?
Is your hand infected? What did the doctor say?
他说会没事的，妈妈
He said it's gonna be fine, Mama.
他说你不用担心，
He said that you don't need to worry,
他说会很棒的，这是他说的
and he said it would be terrific is what he said.
我可能得把他送回呼叫中心了
Well, I just might have to send him back to the call center
为戴文工作，如果你不能给他适当的监督
to work for DeVon if you can't give him proper supervision.
我无法专注于每一秒
I can't keep my eyes on every second.
你到底在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
谁在餐桌底下叫你?
Who's that calling you under the dinner table?
没人，妈妈
Uh, it's no one, Mama.
你在给谁发短信?
Who's that person you're texting?
这是没有人
It's no one.
保守秘密的男孩不会得到奶油蛋羹当甜点
Boys who keep secrets don't get custard for dessert.
那就别告诉她摩托车的事
Don't tell her about the motorcycle, then.
福特旅行车
Ford station wagon.
-等一下
-Hold on one second.
有什么我能帮忙的吗?
Something I can help you with?
科里说我应该把它带来
Corey said I should bring it in.
得到
Get on.
好吧,所以…
Okay, so...
好的
Okay.
右手，煤气左手是你的前-
Uh, right hand, gas. Left hand is your front--
呃,抱歉
Fuck. Uh, sorry.
右手是汽油，也是你的前刹车
Right hand is gas, also your front brake.
左手是你的，离合器
And then left hand is your, uh, clutch.
右脚是你的后刹
Right foot is your back brake.
左脚是移位器什么的
And, uh, left foot is the shifter thingy.
简单
Simple.
听起来并不简单
Doesn't sound simple.
哟,科里
Yo, Corey
来帮我们一把
Come give us a hand.
-嘿,罗恩-嘿,特里
-Hey, Ron. -Hey, Terry.
很抱歉用这种破事打扰你
I'm sorry to bother you with this shit.
我儿子开着辆破车开了三英里
My goddamn son drove three miles on a fucking flat
因为他不知道怎么换轮胎
'cause he doesn't know how to change a tire
在一辆该死的车上
on a goddamn automobile.
该死的天才
Fucking genius.
嗯…我得到了它
Uh... I got it.
是啊，而且要聪明点
Yeah, and fucking smarten up.
我去帮罗纳德，然后把拨浪鼓修好
I'm gonna go help Ronald and then fix the rattle.
你的喋喋不休你的车的,嗯…
Your rattle. Your car's, uh...
我不关心拨浪鼓我是来看你的
I don't care about the rattle. I came to see you.
我们会照顾她的
We'll take care of her.
你得聪明点，孩子
Just got to be a little smarter, kid.
三磅的地面吸盘，就在上面
Three pounds of ground chuck, right here on the top.
谢谢你！-马上回来
Thank you. -Be right back with the lean.
天啊，弗兰克，你听说过蔬菜吗?
Jesus, Frank, have you ever heard of a vegetable?
看看是谁来了
Well, look who it is.
-它们对你有好处-嗯，我喜欢
-They're good for you. -Well, I like to
把肉混在一起给局里的人做炸丸子
mix meats and make croquettes for the guys at the station.
好吧，这听起来很恶心
Okay, that just sounds disgusting.
我喜欢你的头发
I like your hair.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢我,嗯…
Thanks. I, uh...
有一天我把它切了
I just sort of chopped it one day.
只是感觉像是时间到了
It just was-- It felt like time.
是别人修的
Somebody else fixed it.
--是的
-Help. -Yeah.
你的瘦不见了
There goes your lean.
-啊谢谢你,特拉维斯-祝你今天愉快
-Ah. Thank you, Travis. -Have a good day.
-好的—看丫
-Okay. -See ya.
但我跟你说，我觉得我赢得了一条额外的生命
But I tell you, I-I feel like I won an extra life.
我真的
-I really do.
我在当铺买了把吉他，
I got myself a guitar at the pawnshop,
我一直在摆弄它
and I've been fiddling around with that,
我侄女给了我一块罗塞塔石碑
and my niece gave me a Rosetta Stone,
-现在我正在学习日语
-and now I'm learning Japanese.
-那是什么意思?-意思是我丢了我的衬衫
-What does that mean? -It means I lost my shirt.
我认为或者我丢了帽子
-I think. Or I lost my hat.
我不知道我…
I don't know. I...
谢谢
Thanks.
谁知道呢?
who knows?
也许我会飞过去看樱花
Maybe I'll fly over for the cherry blossoms.
在当地人身上测试一下
Test it out on the locals.
你还在埋头写那本书吗?
You still got your nose in that, uh, book you're writing?
你的错这是你的主意
Your fault. It was your idea.
-是什么?
-It was?
-不,我…忘记一个标题吗?
-No, I'm... -Got a title?
刚布置好我的办公室
Just set up my office.
我和艾莉森有个房子
You know, I have a house with Allyson.
我们生活在一起它很好
We're living together. It's nice.
她一直在和一个人说话
You know, she's been talking to this guy.
你可能认识他
You probably know him.
科里坎宁安
Corey Cunningham.
哦,是的我所知道的
Oh, yeah. I do know.
他是个好孩子有一个艰难的假期
He's a good kid. Had a tough break.
很高兴知道有人在外面保护着他
It's nice to know somebody's out there looking out for him.
我喜欢你的脸
I like your face.
我喜欢看你的脸
I mean, I like seeing your face.
所以你
So do you.
我的意思是……
I mean...
我也做我也喜欢见到你
I do, too. I like seeing you, too.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
你在笑什么?
What you smiling about?
你在商店买了什么?
What did you buy at the store?
我很抱歉?-“对不起?”
-I'm sorry? -"I'm sorry?"
我…我很抱歉我不明白你的意思
I'm s-- I'm sorry. I don't understand.
你看到他对我妹妹做了什么吗?
Do you see what he did to my sister?
他杀了她丈夫，还捅了她
He killed her husband, and he stabbed her.
把她的声音
Took her voice
因为你，她不能说话
She cannot speak because of you
你是她的邻居
You were her neighbor,
你连她的名字都不知道，对吧?
and you don't even know her name, do you?
你引诱和激怒了那个人
You tempted and you provoked that man
当你应该离他远点的时候
when you should've left him alone.
劳里
Laurie.
你没事吧?
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
我想看那些樱花
I would like to see those cherry blossoms.
我想你也会喜欢的
And I think you'd like 'em, too.
哇 谁知道该相信什么?
Whoo  Who knows what to believe?
我想是1978年从史密斯格罗夫逃跑的那个人
I think the man who escaped Smith's Grove in 1978
不是那个杀了所有人的人
was not the same man who killed all those people.
真正的迈克尔·迈尔斯那晚被谋杀了，
The real Michael Myers was murdered that night,
那个戴面具的呼吸急促的人是同一个人
and the heavy breather with the mask was the same man
他毒死了教皇约翰·保罗一世
who poisoned Pope John Paul I.
你就在那里 -你好
There you are  -Hi.
我以为我想你了
I thought I missed you.
面具下面是谁?
Who's under the mask?
嗯…我是一个稻草人
Uh... I'm a scarecrow.
什么?
What?
我说我是稻草人-
I said I'm a scarecrow. -
你应该很吓人吗?
Are you supposed to be scary?
我马上就来
I'll be right there.
我马上回来，好吗?
I'll be right back, okay?
我去拿杯喝的
I'm gonna get us a drink.
小心
Watch it
嘿,稻草人
Hey, scarecrow.
看到你喜欢的吗?
See anything you like?
嘿,林赛
Hey, Lindsay.
两个伏特加苏打水两个伏特加苏打水
-Two vodka sodas. -Two vodka sodas.
琳赛，猜猜艾莉森的稻草人是谁
Lindsay, guess who Allyson's scarecrow is.
那个在养老院上了老太太的家伙
The guy that fucked the old lady at the nursing home.
黛比,下降
Deb, drop it.
我在开玩笑
I'm kidding.
其实是科里·坎宁安
It's actually Corey Cunningham,
那个杀了那孩子的人
the guy that killed that kid.
别听她的，艾莉森
Don't listen to her, Allyson.
你想和谁在一起就和谁在一起
You can be with whoever you want to be with.
是的
Yeah.
现在,
And right now,
我和他在一起
I'm with him.
嘿,男人能给我来杯啤酒吗?
Hey, man. Can I get a beer?
嘿
Hey.
你就在这儿跳舞，玩得开心吗?
You're just here dancing and having a good time?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你不好意思吗?哦
You're sorry? Oh.
抱歉?抱歉杀了我儿子?
Sorry? Sorry for killing my son?
我每天醒来，
I wake up every day,
我无法摆脱痛苦
and I can't get past the pain.
它杀死我你明白吗?
It kills me. Do you understand?
你以为你能来这里-
You think you can come here--
不，如果你认为你可以来这里，你就不明白
No, you don't understand if you think you can come here
把你的小面具摘下来
and take off your little mask
祝你和朋友们玩得愉快
and have a good time with your friends.
法官可能会说你是无辜的，但我了解你
A judge might have said you're innocent, but I know you.
我知道这不是意外
I know it was no accident.
这不是意外
It was no accident
你推我儿子是因为你生气了，
You pushed my little boy because you got mad,
你他妈疯了
and you lost your fucking mind
无辜的人不会这么做 不
Innocent people don't do that  No
邪恶的人
Evil people do.
邪恶的
Evil.
科里
Corey
科里,小心 科里
Corey, watch out  Corey
科里
Corey
停止跟我说话-你为什么带我进去?
-Stop. Talk to me. -Why'd you take me in there?
这就是我不出门的原因
It's why I don't go out.
-什么?你,你……
-What? -You just, you...
你把我扔到中间，然后你…
you threw me in the middle of it, and then you...
-我…我…-你是在哪里?
-I... I... -Where were you?
我不知道里面发生了什么
I didn't know what was happening in there.
我只是想，我只是想帮你…
I-I was just trying, I was just trying to help you to just...
我不是你的项目，艾莉森
I'm not your fucking project, Allyson
我只是科里，我知道
I just-- Corey, I know
好吧?我知道那是什么感觉
Okay? I know what it's like to have
每个人看着你，以为他们认识你，
everybody looking at you, thinking that they know you,
以为他们知道你经历了什么，
thinking that they know what you've been through,
但他们没有
but they don't.
但当我看着你，那天我看到你的时候，
But when I look at you-- when I saw you the other day,
我只看到一个人
I just saw a person.
只是一个想要搞清楚的人
Just a person just trying to figure it the fuck out.
试着每天醒来不再害怕，不再孤单
Trying to wake up every day not scared and alone.
但你我之间的区别，艾莉森
But the difference, Allyson, between me and you
人们看着我就像，
is that people look at me like,
“这家伙是谁?”这个怪物是谁?”
"Who is this guy? Who is this monster?"
他们看着你就像他们把你当成幸存者
And they look at you like-- They see you like a survivor.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我明白了你从迈克尔·迈尔斯那里逃了出来
I get it. You survived Michael Myers.
你是奋斗的英雄，去问别人吧
You're a hero with your struggles, and ask anyone.
我是那个神经病保姆我就是那个该死的孩子杀手
I'm the psycho babysitter. I'm the fucking kid killer.
你以为你能治好我，但你不能
And you think you can fix me, but you can't.
我不会让你心痛的
I'll spare you the heartache.
科里
Corey
嘿,很酷的孩子有什么事吗?
Hey, cool kid. What's up?
你要去哪里?
Where you going?
你在这啊，伙计我一直在找你
There you are, man. I've been looking for you.
特里-我想道歉，好吗?
Terry. -I want to apologize, okay?
呃,耶稣基督
Ugh, Jesus Christ.
科里，你怎么看?嗯?
So what do you say, Corey? Huh?
这个怎么样?握手和友谊
How about this? Handshakes and friendship.
别把他晾着，伙计
Don't leave him hanging, dude.
你对这孩子有什么意见?
What is your problem with this kid?
这家伙搞砸了勒巴伦地狱-是的
This guy fucked up the LeBaron. - Hell yeah.
-一元店设计师框架?
-Dollar store designer frames?
哦
Oops.
嘿，让我扶你起来来吧
Hey, let me help you up. Come on.
对不起你都好吗?
-Sorry. -Are you okay?
哇哇给我滚回去
Whoa. Whoa.  Get the fuck back
-嘿 嘿 -回来
-Hey  Hey  -Get back
-回来 -啊哇哇
-Get back  -Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
我只是想帮忙-回来
I'm just trying to help. -Get back
你要杀了我们?和你杀那孩子的方法一样吗?
You gonna murder us? Same way you killed that kid?
你这个小神经病
You little psycho bitch.
你不知道你在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about
-你不知道你在说什么-
-You don't know what you're talking about. -
你就像个混蛋
You just act like a goddamn asshole
因为你父亲把你当孩子看
because your father treats you like one.
这是会传染的,对吧?
It's contagious, right?
妈蛋
Shit.
-你刚才对我说什么?-是对的
-What did you just say to me? -That's right.
我知道有人恨你是什么样子
I know what it looks like when somebody hates you.
你爸爸讨厌你
And your father fucking hates you.
嗯?他讨厌我吗?
-Hmm? He hates me?
比利-他恨我，是吗?
Billy. -He hates me, huh?
-他讨厌我，对吧?-嘿
-He hates me, right? -Hey
比利，别吵了比利
Billy, knock it off. Billy
他讨厌我吗?
-He hates me?
特里，搞什么鬼?
Terry, what the fuck?
-哦,妈蛋
-Oh, shit
-哦,妈蛋哦,我的老天
- Oh, shit.  Oh, my God.
-哦,妈蛋-特里，你做了什么?
-Oh, shit. -Terry, what did you do?
他摔倒了-小混蛋把它弄坏了
-He fell. -Little dick busted it.
他死了吗?-下去看看
Is he dead? - Go down and look.
-不，你下去看看-?
-No, you go down and look. -What the fuck?
我没有推任何人他摔倒了
I didn't push nobody. He fell.
废话他了吗?
-Bullshit. -He fell?
是的，这就是我的故事
Yeah, that's my story.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
现在谁是疯子，特里?谁是神经病?
Who's the psycho now, Terry? Who's the psycho?
小混蛋活该
Little prick deserved it.
快上车
Get in the car, .
我们杀了一个孩子
We killed a kid, man.
来吧
Come on.
嘿,发生了什么?
Hey, what's happening?
只是，这该死的东西我打不起来
Just-- I can't get this fucking thing to turn on.
好吧,好吧换气
Okay, okay. Take a breath.
-好的，深呼吸-让我生气吧
-Okay, take a deep breath. -Just let me be mad
为什么我不能生气?
Why can't I be mad?
你可以
-You can.
你可以生气
You can be mad.
-你会非常非常生气，-(微波炉哔哔声)
-You can be very, very mad, -(microwave beeping)
你可以打碎东西
and you can smash things.
只是小心些而已这是上瘾
Just be careful. It's addictive.
你是对的
You were right.
我喜欢他
I liked him.
是的
Yeah.
-你看到里面那个人了吗?-
-You see that man in there? -
他时不时带人进去
He take people in there now and then.
他为什么让你活着?
Why'd he let you live?
我建议你回去
I say you go back.
你回去把面具给我拿来
You go back in there, and you get me that mask.
我是迈克尔·迈尔斯
I'm Michael Myers.
-操吗?-
-The fuck? -
他还没完呢，你个小混蛋
He not done with you, you little fuck.
嘿
Hey
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
我担心死了
I have been worried sick
科里，我差点打给失踪人口处了
Corey, I almost called the missing persons.
-你怎么了?
-What is going on with you?
科里，我在跟你说话呢
Corey, I'm talking to you.
她一点都不好，该死的
She's no good, damn it.
开门
Open the door.
-开放的大门
-Open the door
你想杀了我吗?
Are you trying to kill me?
科里?科里?
Corey? Corey?
你对升职没什么不满吧?
No hard feelings about the promotion, right?
当然不是这是你应得的
Course not. You deserve it.
我以为马西斯医生没问题
I thought for sure Dr. Mathis
本打算让你当护士长
was gonna make you the charge nurse.
黛布，我能跟你说句话吗?
Deb, can I speak to you a minute?
好吧，黛比，我只告诉你一次…
Okay, Deb, I'm gonna tell you once...
人们创造自己的故事
People create their own stories
做出他们自己的选择
and make their own choices.
他们相信他们想相信的
They believe what they want to believe.
我满怀希望，有远见，
I'm hopeful, with perspective,
我的经历能帮助别人疗伤
that my experience will help others heal.
你得问问自己，我能控制吗，
You have to ask yourself, "Am I in control,
还是大自然控制了我?
"or do the elements control me?
“生命或死亡
"Life or death.
要么自杀，要么开樱花”
Suicide or cherry blossoms."
-你好-
-Hi. -
对不起，我不是故意吓你的
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
我在等艾莉森
I'm just waiting for Allyson.
科里?
Corey?
一切都好吗?
Everything okay?
我昨晚在回家的路上被袭击了
Uh, I got jumped on the way home last night.
这些家伙…
These guys...
加油站的那些孩子在耍我
Those kids from the gas station that were messing with me--
我试着为自己辩护，但他们…
I tried to stand up for myself, and they, um...
哦,我很抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
我来只是想和你谈谈
I just came 'cause I wanted to talk to you.
我想说我很抱歉，还有…
I wanted to say that I'm sorry and there's...
没有借口
no excuse.
但如果你能，求你了，如果你能
But if you could, please, if you could just
和我一起去散步
take a walk with me.
好吗?
Please?
我杀了一个人
I killed someone.
我们在做纸飞机，
We were making paper planes,
但他想看一部怪兽电影
but he wanted to watch a monster movie.
一切都发生得太快了
Everything happened so fast.
我只想过个有趣的夜晚
I just wanted it to be a fun night.
的,只是……一个晚安
That's all, just... a good night.
然后一切都变糟了
And then it all went bad.
我听说发生了什么事
I heard what happened.
我知道这听起来很疯狂，但是当…
I know it sounds crazy, but when...
人们会谈论它，就好像我认识你一样
people would talk about it, it was like I knew you.
就像我在找你一样
Like I was looking for you.
然后她带你来见我
And then she brought you to me.
(高音吹口哨)
(high-pitched whistling)
他做了什么坏事吗?
Has he done something bad?
我不明白你为什么在这里
I don't understand why you're here.
不,不他在看我的孙女
No, no. He's seeing my granddaughter.
其实是我介绍的
I introduced them, actually.
你的孙女应该很幸运
Your granddaughter should be so lucky
和科里这样的男孩在一起
as to be with a boy like Corey.
他很帅他是敏感的
He's handsome. He's sensitive.
我不喜欢他呆在外面
I don't like it when he stays out
夜夜笙歌，但他长大了
all night with girls, but he's grown.
他可以做他想做的事
He can do what he wants.
是的
Yes.
我知道他有他的困难
I know he's had his difficulties.
我的儿子
My son.
整个镇子都反对他
This town turned against him
在杰里米·艾伦出事之后
after the accident with Jeremy Allen.
他们会同情他的
They would've felt for him.
他们会帮助他痊愈的
They would've helped him heal.
但因为你的恶魔消失了
But because your boogeyman disappeared,
他们需要一个新的
they needed a new one.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我父母被杀后，
After my mom and dad were killed,
我只想把这一切都付之一炬
I just wanted to burn it all to the ground
离哈顿菲尔德远点-为什么不离开呢?
-and get away from Haddonfield. -Why not leave?
为什么留下来吗?
Why stay?
我所有的记忆都在这里
All my memories are here.
我觉得你父母都被杀了
I think both your parents got killed
你奶奶为此感到内疚，
and your grandma feels guilty about it,
所以她要让你成为她的孩子
so she's making you her child.
如果你能在治疗前见她一面，
If you could've seen her before therapy,
清醒了，而我…
sobering up, and me...
我只是害怕会发生什么事
I'm just terrified to think what would happen
如果她孤身一人如果我走了
if she were all alone if I left.
所以呢，你得留在这里，保护她
So, what, you got to stay here, protect her
从自己到永远吗?
from herself forever?
看起来……
Look...
很抱歉我在聚会上失去了理智
I'm sorry I lost my head at the party
我走开了
and I walked away.
这是一个错误
That was a mistake.
当我看着你，我…
When I look at you, I...
我知道我可以告诉你真相
I know I can tell you the truth.
我不怕这些人
I'm not afraid of these people.
我不再害怕了
I'm not afraid anymore.
你说你想把它烧了，
You tell me that you want to burn it down,
或者你告诉我你想把它烧为平地
or you tell me you want to burn it to the ground.
嘿一周两次
Hey. Twice in one week.
很酷您热责备
Pretty cool. Hot diggity.
嘿，你说你…你会打电话的
Hey, you said you, uh... you were gonna call.
你是…你本来想打电话的，但你没打
You were... you were gonna call, but you didn't call.
不，我欠你一个电话
No, I owe you a call.
我是……我做错什么了吗?
Did I... did I do something wrong or...
我与某人
I'm with someone.
哦哦
Oh. Oh.
哦不好意思
Oops. Uh, sorry for that.
对不起，打扰你了
I'm sorry for the intrusion.
嗯，嗯，你知道的，这是…这是乔·格里洛的，呃…
Well, um, you know, it's, uh... it's Joe Grillo's, uh...
嗨,乔 嘿
Hey, Joe  Hey.
乔·格里洛的生日
Joe Grillo's birthday today.
乔·罗斯，他做了个海绵蛋糕
And Joe Ross, uh, he made a sponge cake.
你们俩想过来吃点东西吗
You two want to stop by, get a slice
-在你们做了什么之后?我们很好
-after whatever you guys are doing? -We're good.
哦好的,你很好
Oh. Okay, you're good.
让我告诉你，这…
Let me tell you, it's, uh...
如果你改变主意了，还有…
If you change your mind, there's...
她说我们和好了
She said we're good
伙计，你有什么问题吗?
Hey, buddy, you got a problem?
我们很好
We're good.
哦,妈蛋
Oh, shit.
埃里森
Allyson.
所以你打电话给故意杀人罪先生
So you call Mr. Aggravated Manslaughter
晚上睡不着的时候?
at night when you can't sleep?
当你在噩梦中看到恶魔的时候?
When you see the Boogeyman in your nightmares?
和他在一起你觉得安全吗?
You feel safe with this guy?
嘿,男人
Hey, man.
折腾了
Messing around.
埃里森
Allyson.
不,不,不
Nah, nah, nah.
心理你不错,Mulaney吗?
-Psycho. -You good, Mulaney?
一切都很好一切都很好
It's all good. It's all good.
我们要去揍谁吗?
We need to go kick somebody's ass?
不,不我得到这个
No, no. I got this.
把它全烧了吧
Just burn it all to the ground.
我来点火柴
I'll light the match.
你想进来吗?
Do you want to come in?
另一个晚上
Another night.
啊,操
Ah, fuck
嘿
Hey
你不能惹道格·穆兰尼
You don't fuck with Doug Mulaney
你在哪里?嗯?
Where are you? Huh?
你说那是个意外
You say it was an accident.
但我知道你做了什么
But I know what you did.
我要打烂你的脸，你个小混蛋
I'm gonna fuck your face up, you little shit.
那是什么?
The fuck is that?
的帮助
Help.
告诉我怎么做
Show me how to do it.
起来，起来，起来
Get up, get up, get up.
起来
Get up
是谁?
Who is it?
是我
It's me.
哦,我的老天你还好吗?
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
我不知道我怎么了
I don't know what's happening to me.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
看着我
Look at me.
这是谁干的?
Who did this to you?
看着我
Look at me.
迈克尔·迈尔斯让你活下来了吗?
Did Michael Myers let you live?
还是你逃跑了?
Or did you escape?
(颤抖的呼吸)
(trembling breaths)
疼吗?
Does it hurt?
不不
No. No.
我妈妈救了我
My mother saved me.
你和他上床了，是吗?
You're fucking him, aren't you?
从某种程度上来说，这是哈顿菲尔德的完美故事
It's, like, the perfect story of Haddonfield in a way.
可爱的小女孩爱上了当地的流氓
Cute young girl falls for local creep.
想象一下，如果你的祖母有
Imagine if your grandmother had
爱上了迈克尔·迈尔斯
fallen in love with Michael Myers.
但她没有我听说她捅了他
But she didn't. I heard she stabbed him
脖子上被针织针扎了
in the neck with a fucking knitting needle.
你怎么了，黛布?
What's your problem, Deb?
你跟我说话就像我不存在一样
You talk to me like I'm not even here.
你就不能闭上你的臭嘴吗?
Do you ever just shut your goddamn mouth?
我知道,对吧?
I know, right?
我知道我说得太多了
I know I talk too much.
我只是对那些鬼东西太兴奋了
I just get so excited about all that Boogeyman bullshit.
嗯不我要否决这笔交易
Uh-uh. No. I-I'm vetoing that trade.
马克防守最后一名时的第二接球手
Your second receiver for Mark's last-place defense
勾结的味道
reeks of collusion.
这不是一个直接的交换
It's not a straight-up swap.
你想用水准赢得冠军吗?
You want to win the championship with class?
停止欺骗
Stop cheating.
我一直看到他的眼睛
I keep seeing his eyes.
我们是在说迈克尔还是这孩子?
Are we talking about Michael or this kid?
迈克尔的眼睛盯着科里
Michael's eyes in Corey.
琳赛，我很确定
Lindsay, I was so sure.
就像第一次一样
Just like the first time.
嗨,罗杰
Hey, Roger.
我想让你见个人
There's someone I want you to meet.
我一直喜欢科里
I always liked Corey.
你知道，有些孩子，你能看出来他们很讨厌，
You know, some kids, you can tell they're a pain in the ass,
但科里是个好孩子
but Corey was a good kid.
我只是无法想象他会有这种能力
And I just couldn't imagine he'd be capable
故意伤害别人
of hurting anyone on purpose.
但这次审判，我…
But with the trial, I...
我刚开始琢磨各种理论，然后…
just started spinning with theories, and...
最后我想，
and eventually I thought,
“放弃它你永远都不会结束的
"Give it up. You're never gonna get closure.
根本就没有这回事”
There's no such thing."
几年过去了，我偶尔会看到他，
A couple of years go by, and I'd see him every now and then,
看看人们是怎么躲着他的
see the way people avoided him
或者他们在他背后做鬼脸，
or how they made faces behind his back,
说实话，这让我很生气
which, if I'm honest, pissed me off.
因为我觉得他们带走了我的痛苦…
Because I felt like they took my pain...
...我的绝望,
...my despair,
他们把它变成了关于他们的
and they made it about them.
然后，昨天，我在上班的路上
And then, yesterday, I'm on my way to work.
他就在这里
There he is.
我想"我要说点什么，
And I think, "I'm gonna say something,
“证明我妻子是错的
"prove my wife wrong.
让我们想办法原谅这个孩子吧”
Let's find a way to forgive this kid."
我把车停在他旁边，他看着我，
And I pull up next to him, and he looks at me,
那不是他
and it's not him.
至少不是在眼睛里
At least not in the eyes.
我不知道，伙计
And I don't know, man.
我脖子后面的汗毛都竖起来了
The hairs on the back of my neck stood up.
就在那时，我觉得我得到了答案
Right then, I felt like I got my answer.
以前给我们修剪草坪的那个孩子没有杀我儿子
The kid who used to mow our lawn didn't kill my son.
我知道
I know that.
但我在路边看到的那个人
But the guy I saw on the side of the road
走上了一条黑暗的道路
was down a dark path.
是镇上的人在事故后这么对他的吗?
Did the town do this to him after the accident?
还是一直都在?
Or was it always there?
我讲的笑话你都在笑，
You're just laughing at all my jokes,
-不你?-(Deb笑)
-aren't you? -(Deb laughs)
哦,我的老天
Oh, my God.
好吧,Alexa
All right, Alexa.
播放Rob Galbraith的《用你的眼睛告诉我》
Play "Tell Me With Your Eyes" by Rob Galbraith.
ALEXA:这是“用你的眼睛告诉我……”
ALEXA: Here's "Tell Me With Your Eyes..."
这房子太…
This house is so...
富有
rich.
宝贝，我等这一刻等了一整天了
Baby, I have been waiting all day for this.
我一直保存着这瓶法式香槟
I've been saving this bottle of Au Bon Climat.
你今天在办公室的样子真他妈性感
You looked so fucking hot at the office today.
介意我……
Mind if I...
卧室在走廊尽头
Bedroom's down the hall.
清理洗澡
Clean up. Take a shower.
事实上，我们在那里见
In fact, I'll meet you in there.
是的,是的
Yes, yes.
是的
Yes.
天呐(点击的舌头)
Holy shit. (clicks tongue)
家里有医生吗?
Is there a doctor in the house?
是的,宝贝好吧
Yeah, baby. All right.
得到了奶酪我们有饼干
Got the cheese. We got the crackers.
我们已经做好了准备
We're ready.
马修斯博士吗?
Dr. Mathis?
求你了，求你了，求你了求你了，求你了，求你了
Please, please, please, please. Please, please, please, please.
911年……
911...
事故发生后,
After the accident,
我会骑着自行车过来，坐在屋顶上
I'd ride my bike over here and I'd sit up on this roof.
我抬头看着那座塔
And I'd look up at that tower.
不知道我能不能爬到山顶
Wonder if I could climb to the top.
它在召唤我
It was summoning me.
就像瞭望塔或灯塔在召唤我回到过去的生活
Like a watchtower or beacon calling me to live my old life.
重新快乐起来
To be happy again.
我也有类似的东西
I have something like that, too.
它总是给我希望，你知道，事情会
It always gave me hope, you know, things would--
也许一切都能回到过去
well, maybe somehow things would go back
回到他们过去的样子
to the way they used to be.
之前一切都改变了
Before everything changed.
感染
Infected.
我得远离所有认识我的人
I got to get away from everybody who knows me.
但我不，我…
But I don't, I...
我不想一个人去
I don't want to go alone.
科里,来吧
Corey, come on.
停止
-Stop.
我觉得你是害怕没有足够的绷带
I think you're scared that you don't have enough bandages
让我振作起来
to keep me together.
科里，你在…?
Corey, what are you...?
你都好吗?
-Are you okay?
怎么，你疯了吗?
What, are you insane?
怎么，你想自杀吗?
What, are you trying to kill yourself?
我对永生不感兴趣
I'm not interested in immortality.
这到底是怎么回事?
The hell is going on out here?
这是私人领地
Yo, this is private property.
不管你做什么都不安全…
Not safe to be doing whatever the hell you do...
科里坎宁安
Corey Cunningham.
你在外面干什么，你个丑八怪?
What you doing out here, you ugly motherfucker?
-科里，别说了-你会吓到所有的孩子
- Corey, stop it. -You gonna scare all the kids.
你停止
You stop.
我不知道你在跟谁说话，
I don't know who the fuck you talking to,
但我知道你是谁
but, uh, I know who you are.
我知道劳里·斯特罗德的事
Yeah, I know the Laurie Strode story.
她取笑一个脑损伤的男人，然后他就崩溃了
She teased a man with brain damage, and then he snapped.
看看你
Look at you.
你现在想出名了吗?
You gonna make a little name for yourself now, huh?
和这个蠢婊子在一起
Walking around with this dumb bitch right here.
你从来不闭嘴
You never shut up.
到处都能听到他的声音
Hear his voice everywhere.
你他妈说对了
Oh, you're goddamn right you do.
一旦威利进入你的耳朵，
And once Willie get in your ear,
就像你最喜欢的歌在你脑海里挥之不去
it's like your favorite song stuck in your head.
你们都给我滚出去
Y'all get the hell up off my property
在我把你们都搞死之前
before I fuck y'all up.
-好的
-All right.
你是对的
You're right.
让我们做它
Let's do it.
我不想再待在哈顿菲尔德了
I don't want to be in Haddonfield anymore.
我想和你在一起
I want to be with you.
我能在你身上闻到她的味道
I can smell her on you.
她想把你从我身边夺走，是吗?
She's trying to take you away from me, isn't she?
你每天晚上都去那里
That's where you go every night.
好吧，我说去吧
Well, I say go.
你现在就去
You go right now
滚出我的房子
Get out of my house
哦,不不
Oh, no. No.
我希望你找到真爱
I hope you find love.
埃里森?
Allyson?
很高兴见到你
It's nice to see you.
你知道，有两种邪恶
You know, there are two kinds of evil.
一种是作为外部力量存在的邪恶
There's the evil that exists as an external force
这威胁到部落的福祉
that threatens the well-being of the tribe.
生存取决于理解和意识
Survival depends on understanding and awareness
以及对日常生活的身体威胁的恐惧
and fear of physical threat to our daily lives.
另一种邪恶存在于我们体内
The other kind of evil lives inside us.
比如疾病或感染
Like a sickness or an infection.
更危险的是我们可能不知道自己被感染了
It's more dangerous because we may not know we're infected.
我是个坏人吗?
Am I a bad person?
是吗?
Are you?
嗯…
Well...
...我们都是满不在乎的
...we're both fucked-up.
我想帮你，科里-
-I want to help you, Corey. -
让我来帮你
Let me help you.
或者让我帮你找帮手
Or let me find help for you.
你不能拥有她
You can't have her.
艾莉森不适合这段感情，
Allyson is not equipped for this relationship,
我不会让她受到伤害的
and I will not let her get hurt.
所以离我远点…
So stay the fuck away...
你开始这个
You started this
是你带我来的 你邀请我
You brought me in  You invited me
但你才是罪魁祸首
But you're the one to blame.
“你想做，还是你想让我做?”
"You want to do it, or you want me to?"
如果我不能拥有她…
If I can't have her...
...没有人会
...no one will.
你想帮艾莉森吗?让她过她自己的生活
You want to help Allyson? Let her live her life.
她现在有我了
She has me now.
你应该让步
You should give in.
你应该向你的那种感觉屈服
You should surrender to that feeling you had
你第一次看着他的眼睛
the first time you ever looked into his eyes.
你暗地里希望迈克尔回来找你
You secretly hope Michael comes back for you.
我是神经病
I'm the psycho.
你才是怪胎
You're the freak show.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我们得走了
We need to leave.
现在不行我的工作
I can't right now. I'm working.
那么,今晚
Tonight, then.
9点见好吗?
Will you meet me at 9:00?
在74街的餐厅
At the diner off 74.
我们得谈谈你祖母的事
We need to talk about your grandmother.
她想杀了我
She wants to kill me.
-什么?-是的
-What? -Yeah.
我再也受不了了
I can't take it anymore.
是时候和哈顿菲尔德说再见了
It's time to say goodbye to Haddonfield.
你有我需要的东西
You got something I need.
(的)
(both grunting)
(科里大叫呻吟)
(Corey shouts, groans)
你只是个戴着万圣节面具的人
You're just a man in a Halloween mask.
你现在打算怎么办?
What are you gonna do now?
(喘着粗气)
(both breathing heavily)
上他后
-Call him after.
我不想去你家，伙计
I don't want to go to your house, man.
你爸总是对我们大吼大叫
Your dad always fucking yells at us.
太坏你应该有你自己的
Too fucking bad. You should've got your own.
反正也不应该有这些东西
Shouldn't have any of these anyway.
为什么我们不能去她家?她才是那个有钱的人
Why can't we go to her house? She's the one that's rich.
-哦,什么?是的开枪什么?
-Oh, what? Yeah. Shoot. What the fuck?
什么?
What?
他死了 进入
He's dead  Get in
哦,妈蛋妈蛋
Oh, shit. Shit.
你找到要找的东西了吗?
Did you find what you're looking for?
我想你的旅行一定很愉快
I imagine you're going on a wonderful trip.
-你打算告诉我吗?有什么区别吗?
-Were you gonna tell me? -What difference does it make?
这很重要，艾莉森
It makes a big difference, Allyson.
我觉得他有能力造成真正的伤害
I feel he is capable of real harm.
这是困扰你的吗?
Is that what bothers you?
是怀疑还是妄想?
Is it suspicion or paranoia?
直觉吗?一个暗示吗?
Intuition? An inkling?
你知道吗?
You got an inkling?
我去了他家我见到了他的母亲
I went to his home. I met his mother.
我知道他告诉我
I know. He told me.
所以,你是什么?你现在跟踪他了?
So, you're what? You're stalking him now?
-不-你在威胁他
-No. -And you're threatening him.
-你对他说了什么?-我在他身上看到了同样的东西
-What did you say to him? -I-I see the same thing in him
-我在迈克尔身上看到的迈克尔
-that I saw in Michael. -Michael.
迈克尔·迈尔斯就是你
Michael Myers is who you are.
你没听我说，艾莉森
You're not listening to me, Allyson.
我是在保护你
I am trying to protect you.
我不需要你的保护
I don't want your protection
但你可以过上好日子，艾莉森
But you-you can have a good life, Allyson.
一个好的生活
A good life.
只是不是和他
Just not with him.
你假装你已经向前看了，但这都是扯淡
You pretend like you moved on, but it's bullshit.
你只是对死亡着迷
You're actually just obsessed with death,
就像一场游戏
like it's some sort of game.
不完成任务你是不会休息的
And you're not gonna rest until you've finished it
或者直到所有人都像你一样痛苦
or until everybody else is as fucking miserable as you are
我得在这镇子杀人之前离开这里
I need to get out of here before this town kills
唯一一个让我有感觉的人
the one person that actually makes me feel something.
-他走在一条黑暗的道路上
-He is on a dark path
我不会让这种事发生在你身上
I'm not gonna let this happen to you
你一定要相信我
You have to believe me
相信你?
Believe you?
你想让我相信你?
You want me to believe you?
因为你引起的歇斯底里
Because of the hysteria that you caused
当我信任你的时候，我的朋友们都死了
when I trusted you, my friends are dead.
我的父母都死了
My parents are dead.
你才是那个会伤害别人的人
You're the one that's capable of fucking harm
(耳机里传来的枪声和刺耳的轮胎声)
(gunfire and tires screeching over headphones)
你确定他在这里翻的吗，伙计?
You sure he turned in here, dude?
是啊，好像是他的藏身处
Yeah, it's like his hideout or something.
那是他工作的地方
It's where he works.
-他的作品很烂-实际上是垃圾场
-His work is a dump. -It actually is a dump.
好吧，但说真的，他在哪?
Okay, no, but seriously, where is he?
有自行车-该死，哥们，靠边停车
There's the bike. -Shit, dude, pull over.
这太疯狂了
This is gonna be so crazy.
小的走了比利，你能快点吗?
-Let's go.  Billy, can you hurry up?
科里 你是压扁我
-Corey  -You're squishing me.
-老天-他去了?
-God. -Where'd he go?
出来,科里
Come out, Corey
科里，我只想吻你和好，伙计
Corey, I just want to kiss and make up, my man
-来吧 -别当废物了
-Come on  -Stop being a punk
科里 -你在哪儿，伙计?
Corey  -Where you at, man?
我让你看看你弄坏我爸爸的车会有什么后果
I'll show you what happens when you mess with my dad's car
-我们能快点吗?
- -Can we hurry this up, man?
哦，我有个主意
Oh, I got an idea.
比利，倒车
Billy, back the car up.
的赌注
Bet.
抓住链我们走吧
Grab that chain. Let's go.
特里，办公室里有人
: Terry, there's somebody in the office.
别犯贱了
Stop being a chickenshit.
把它放在轮子上好吧?
Run it through the wheel. All right?
我们要把它绑在车后面，
We're gonna tie it to the back of the car,
然后拖它，直到什么都不剩
and then we'll drag it till there's nothing left.
Dusty-ass自行车
Dusty-ass bike.
妈蛋
-Shit.
小的,比利比利 头里,特里快点,伙计
-Let's go, Billy. Billy  -Come on, Terry. Hurry up, man.
曾经有人在这里比利
-Someone's here. -Billy
来吧,比利 让我们抓住这个混蛋
Come on, Billy  Let's get this punk
我们走吧
Let's go
哦,我的老天比利
Oh, my God. Billy.
比利，你想干什么，伙计?吸自己的……
Billy, what are you trying to do, man? Suck your own...
哦,我的老天
Oh, my God
什么?
What the fuck?
:特里?
: Terry?
怎么了?
What's wrong?
比利的死
Billy's dead
-什么?什么?
-What?  What?
-你在说什么?
-What are you talking about?
-哦,妈蛋
-Oh, shit.
史黛西吗?史黛西吗?
-Stacy? Stacy?
什么……发生了什么?
What... what's happening?
该死的
Damn it
史黛西
Stacy
救命，救命，救命，救命
Help, help, help, help
的帮助 你得帮帮我 帮帮我
Help  You got to help me  Help me
哦,我的老天
Oh, my God
跟我说话
Speak to me.
你还好吗?你还好吗?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
保持冷静我会把你弄出去的
Stay calm. I'm gonna get you out of here.
别担心我会救你出来的
Don't worry. I'm gonna get you out.
-试着冷静
-Try to be calm.
这是加载
It's loaded.
待在这里
Stay here.
我不想死
: I don't want to die.
-我 帮帮我 -嘿,嘿
-Help me  Help me  - Hey, hey
等一等等一等静静不动
Hold on. Hold on. Hold still.
不要动 我会帮你取下来的
Hold still  I'll get it off you.
他在那儿
There he is
科里?
Corey?
我有你
I got you
-我抓住你了，你这个变态 -不,不
-I got you, you fucking psycho  - No, don't
史黛西史黛西
Stacy. Stacy.
神
God.
哦,我的老天
Oh, my God.
特里-！
Terry. -
特里
Terry.
-老天哦,我的老天哦,我的老天
-God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
史黛西在哪儿?
Where's Stacy?
史黛西死了
Stacy's dead.
你死了
You're dead, too.
-什么?特里
-What?  -Terry
不
No.
哦,妈蛋
Oh, shit.
这是柠檬皮的皮屑
It's the zest of a lemon peel.
给了一个新的转折
Gives a little fresh twist.
蓝莓显然很辣
So the blueberries, obviously, are really hot.
等一切都准备好了，
And then when it's all ready to go,
我们去把奶油冻起来，然后打发……
we'll go and freeze the custard and then whip...
罗纳德?
Ronald?
我有衣服
I have laundry.
我可以把它放在你的梳妆台里，
I can put it in your dresser,
或者我可以把它放在这个篮子里
or I can leave it in this basket here.
...把这个容器放在冰箱里
...this container and put it in the freezer
大概，半小时到一小时吧
for about, oh, half an hour to an hour
所以它会变硬
so it'll firm up.
现在我们要吃了它
Now we're gonna eat it.
看起来不错
That looks good.
一点冰淇淋，一点饼干……
A little ice cream, a little cookie...
热线开通了，我们正在接受请求
Ooh, the hotline is open, and we are taking requests.
复活之歌
Songs for the resurrection.
怎样才能把我们的怪物弄出来?
What's gonna get our monster out?
给我们点可以尖叫的东西?
Give us something to scream about?
来电者，你正在广播中
Caller, you're on the air.
威利，你应该这样
Willie, you should be
为自己利用这些悲剧而感到羞愧
ashamed of yourself exploiting these tragedies.
哈顿菲尔德现在有三个人失踪
There are three missing people right now in Haddonfield.
注意，先生，在和怪物战斗时，
"Beware," sir, "that when fighting monsters,
“你自己不会变成一个怪物，
"you yourself do not become a monster,
"因为当你凝视深渊时，
"for when you gaze long into the abyss,
深渊也向你凝视”
the abyss gazes also into you."
尼采也说过:“没有音乐……”
Nietzsche also said, "Without music..."
＂...生活将是一个错误”
"...life would be a mistake."
我能为您效劳吗?
Can I help you?
伙计，你到底是谁?
Hey, man, who the hell are you?
嘿，搞什么…哦
Hey, what the f... Oh
阿廖沙,对不起
Allyson, I'm sorry.
我为我说的话道歉
I'm sorry for what I said.
我很抱歉拜托
I'm sorry. Please.
我只想让你回家
And I just want you to come home.
911. -是的
911. -Yes.
我要报告一起自杀案
I would like to report a suicide.
磨坊尽头路1206号
1206 Mill's End Road.
你真以为我会自杀吗?
Did you really think I'd kill myself?
-我已经很努力了…(呻吟)
-I have tried so hard... -(groaning)
...要有怜悯之心，寻求怜悯
...to have compassion and find mercy.
但这有什么意义呢?
But what's the point?
你是来杀我的，动手吧
You came here to kill me, so do it.
我们都知道真相
You know, we all learn the truth
关于彼此
about each other eventually.
你真的以为
Did you really think
艾莉森会和你在一起吗
that Allyson was gonna be with you?
如果我不能拥有她…
If I can't have her...
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
你做了什么?
What did you do?
你对他做了什么?
What did you do to him?
不,不
No, no.
不不
No. No.
你为什么要这么做?
Why did you do this?
-不科里,回来回来了
-No. -Corey, come back. Come back.
不,不
No, no.
你
You
阿廖沙,劳里在哪儿?
Allyson, where's Laurie?
我们是来接电话的她报警说有人自杀
We're responding to a call. She called in a suicide.
不
No
我逃离了你
I've run from you.
我一直在追你
I have chased you.
我试过控制你
I have tried to contain you.
我试着原谅你
I have tried to forgive you.
我还以为你是恶魔呢
I thought maybe you were the Boogeyman.
不
No.
你只是一个快要停止呼吸的人
You're just a man who's about to stop breathing.
这样做
Do it.
做到
Do it
这样做
Do it.
不
No
我不会让这种事发生在你身上
I'm not gonna let this happen to you.
没关系
It's okay.
别挡道待在这里
Get out of the way. Stay here.
只是退后
Just stay back.
劳里
-Laurie
迈克尔
Michael.
他死了
He's dead.
不够死
Not dead enough.
我们不是这么做的
This isn't how we do it.
你们都疯了你在做什么?
You're all crazy.  What are you doing?
你要带他去哪?
Where are you taking him?
哈顿菲尔德该开始疗伤了
Time for Haddonfield to start healing.
-让他们都看看
-Let's show them all.
事情不是这样的
This is not how it works.
这是今晚
It is tonight.
无线电静默更强
Uh, stronger on radio silence.
这一定是个命令
That's got to be a command.
收到-副本
Copy that. - Copy.
小的走了
-Let's go.
迈克尔·迈尔斯的尸体
The body of Michael Myers
在午夜游行中被处理掉了
was disposed of in a midnight procession.
没有墓碑，没有纪念碑
There would be no tombstone, no memorial.
谜团被解开了，
The mysteries were put to bed,
我们所说的故事会随着时间的流逝而消失
and the story as we told it was to fade with time.
科里的事你说得对
You were right about Corey.
我知道他杀了那些人
I know he killed those people.
他被邪恶吞噬了
He was consumed by evil.
哈顿菲尔德的事件
The events of Haddonfield
造成了如此多的暴力和流血事件
that created so much violence and bloodshed
终于解决
finally had resolve.
有报道证实迈克尔·迈尔斯
Reports now confirm that Michael Myers
在袭击未遂后被杀
has indeed been killed dead after an attempted assault
哈顿菲尔德居民劳里·斯特罗德的尸体
of Haddonfield resident Laurie Strode.
多么难以置信的生存故事啊
What an incredible story of survival
经过我们当地社区几十年的动乱
through decades of disturbances in our local community.
最后……
Finally...
新的开始在前面
New beginnings lay ahead.
我们所有人都会感到恐惧，
Fear moves through all of us,
我们决定何时投降
and we decide when to surrender.
我已经和我的恶魔说了再见，
I've said goodbye to my boogeyman,
但事实是邪恶不会消失
but the truth is evil doesn't die.
它改变了形状
It changes shape.
我想让你知道我在想你
I wanted you to know I was thinking about you.
我想感谢你所做的一切
I want to thank you for what you did.
享受
Enjoy.
你说那些樱花是什么意思?
What was it you were saying about those cherry blossoms?